Well 幸运的是 由于我们
luckily, since we've
been using an 一直以来使用的都是仿真器
emulator all along,
we can actually fake anything,我们实际上可以虚构任何东西 因为如果你想想
because if you think about it,
this entire device is 整个设备一开始都是虚构的
all fake to start with.
Now if you open up the 如果你打开“额外设置” (Extra Settings) 窗口
Extra Settings window,
you'll find an 你可以找到一个位置选项
option for location
where you can set the 在此设置设备的坐标 甚至是
device's coordinates and even
its altitude. 高度
Here, I've inputted the 我在这里输入了悉尼的坐标
coordinates for Sydney
and hopped over to 并在 Google 地图中跳到了它
it in Google Maps.
Additionally, you can set up a 此外 你可以设置 GPX 或 KML 格式
file of either GPX or KML
format and launch it to 的文件 并启动它以自定义速度模拟
simulate a path of coordinates
with custom speeds.坐标路径
Here's an example of 这里有一个 KML 文件格式的示例
a KML file format.
I've loaded that file 我将该文件加载到了这里的播放中
into this playback here.
And let's watch it go. 我们来看它播放
Pretty cool, huh? 挺酷的 对吧？
Now however, testing 但是 测试地理围栏有点棘手
Geofences is tricky.
Remember that Geofences 记住地理围栏依赖网络、Wi-Fi 数据
rely on network, Wi-Fi data,
and the last known GPS. 和最新已知 GPS
And using this data, it  它仅在需要时使用此数据
only refreshes the last known
GPS when it needs to. 刷新最新已知 GPS
Because remember, refreshing 因为记住 刷新最新已知 GPS
the last known GPS
is a very battery-heavy 是一项非常耗电的操作
operation.
Now unfortunately, when we  不幸的是 当我们在仿真器上模拟 GPS 时
do spoof GPS on an emulator,
it doesn't automatically 它不会自动更新最新已知 GPS
update the last known GPS.
However, there is 但是 我们可以使用一个技巧
a trick we can use
to be able to trigger a 来从仿真器触发地理围栏
Geofence from an emulator.
Now while our app 虽然我们的应用不会自动
doesn't automatically
get the latest GPS location,获取最新的 GPS 位置 但手机上的其他应用
other apps on the phone,
such as Google Maps, can help 如 Google 地图 可帮助我们获取 GPS 位置
us to acquire the GPS location.
If I simply open up Google Maps, 如果我只是打开 Google 地图 它会强制执行新的 GPS 更新
it will force a new GPS update
and will hence refresh 因此会刷新最新的 GPS 位置
the latest GPS location.
This will most likely trigger a 这很可能会立即触发地理围栏转换
Geofence transition immediately
if the device was（如果设备在这样的地理围栏内）
inside such Geofence.